Warning! The footage you are about to watch is of a sensitive nature
and although it may not be suitable for all viewers, it is for the glory of God.
This young woman has arrived at The Synagogue Church Of All Nations
seeking solution to her problem.
We can see her arm being held livelessly at her side,
afflicted with a terrible ulcer at the top of her hand.
The severity of her wound has attracted flies and infection as it has grown and eaten away her flesh.
One can only imagine the pain and discomfort that the open sore has caused her,
rendering her hand useless.
Debilitated at such a young age, she is desperately searching for someone somewhere to heal her wound.
As Isaiah 53:5 reassures us:
Our healing is paid for and offered freely.
By Christ's wound we are healed.
I have a house girl. She confessed that she was an obanje (possessed)
and she delivered an egg.
Immediately, I carried the egg and burnt it.
Since then, my hand that I used to carry the egg has become rotten.
She laboured as if she wanted to deliver a baby.
She opened her legs and said, "Aunty, it's coming, it's coming".
Behold, I saw an egg, a live egg came out of her private part.
With my little faith, I carried the egg, put fire on it and burnt it.
This is the hand that I used to burn it.
The doctor said that it would be amputated.
I ran to the man of God to help me. Please, help me, Man of God,
so that they would not amputate my hand.
The woman said that her house maid confessed that she was a witch
and gave birth to an egg.
She explained how she took the egg with her own hand and burnt it
and that was how the hand ulcer appeared.
Can you just say your prayer; ask for the mercy and favour of God.
Lord Jesus, forgive me; have mercy on me.
Have mercy on me so that I can be delivered and
my hand will not be cut off.
Father, forgive her, in Jesus' name. Amen.
You are free. Go.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
After the prayer of Prophet T.B. Joshua,
the woman came back to The SCOAN to testify to the miraculous healing she had received.
An arm which was once left to be amputated
has now being totally restored back to life.
We can see how the mighty hand of God has brought divine healing to her flesh.
An agony she once felt is a thing of the past.
Jesus Christ, the Master Healer, has healed her effectually.
Glory be to God.
Before and After
Who is like my Jesus?
Who is like my Jesus in this world?
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Anthonia. I came from Abuja (Nigeria) to give my testimony.
The God of T.B. Joshua, I have never seen your type o.
This kind God o - blessed be Your holy name.
I had a problem with my hand. That was what brought me to The SCOAN.
I had a hand ulcer.
I was happily married when I employed a house girl to live with me.
It was the house girl who separated me from my husband.
The house girl confessed that she was a witch and after that,
she delivered an egg in my presence; I don't know how that could happen.
I was confused and didn't know what to do.
I used my hand to pick up the egg after which I set fire to it and burned it.
The next day, my hand became swollen.
My hand began to hurt me.
I was taken to different places but nobody could help me.
Doctors wanted to amputate my hand. I cried.
As I was watching Emmanuel TV, my in-law advised that I should be taken to see T.B. Joshua.
That was how they took me to this place and the man of God prayed for me.
Brothers and sisters, come and see.
After the man of God prayed for me, the ulcer disappeared!
I am healed and there is nothing that I can't use this hand to do.
I wash clothes, cook and do everything with this hand.
My advice to people is that they should believe and trust in God and
they should have faith.
Whatever the situation, there is nothing that God cannot do.
Here was my last bus stop. I believed that God would heal me;
I came and I got my healing. Have faith and believe in God.
God that did it for me will do it for everybody.
Testimony Time
RV: Mel Flowers 23/03/2019